To be a Negro in this country and to be relatively conscious is to be in a state of rage all of the
time, James Baldwin. How does that speak to you? I understand. I see that, especially when you
think when he was writing. When someone shows you who they are, believe them, Ms. Maya Angelou.
And she told me that personally. Flex. All right. And our last one, you better check yourself
before you wreck yourself. Before you wreck yourself? That is correct.
They're right. How many times do you later in life wish you'd just been in your tongue and said
nothing? These days, it's so easy to send a text you'll regret later or to send an email you'll
regret later. It's like nobody has any impulse control today. Everything's going like this.
So, you know, that's my first time interviewing a political candidate. And I will say this,
and I stand on this and I said it to her face. I'm gonna say it here.